Register of the William T. Poole collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Un-American Activities Subject File, 1920-1976 (Box 51-231.)
  - Freedom House. Circular letter, report, and clipping, 1943-1968 (Folder 102: 11)
  - Freedom Now Committee [Los Angeles]. Informant's report, and clipping, 1966 (Folder 102: 12)
  - Freedom Now for Lt. Howe Committee. Leaflets and circular letter, 1966 (Folder 102: 13)
  - Freedom Now Party. HUAC memorandum, ca. 1964 (Folder 102: 14)
  - Freedom Party [University of Florida]. Flyers, and announcement, 1965-1966 (Folder 102: 15)
  - Freedom Socialist Party. Clipping, 1969 (Folder 102: 16)
  - Freedomways (Folder 102)
    - General. Letters, circulars, commemorative issuances re W. E. B. DuBois and Paul Robeson, and HUAC memoranda, 1962-1972 (Folder 102: 17)
    - Serial issues (Folder 102)
      - 1963 (Folder 102: 18)
      - 1968 (Folder 103: 1)
      - 1969 (Folder 103: 2)
      - 1970 (Folder 103: 3)
      - 1971 (Folder 104: 1)
      - 1972 (Folder 104: 2)
  - Fresno Writers and Artists against the War in Vietnam. Clipping, 1967 (Folder 104: 3)
  - Friends and Neighbors of David Hyun [re deportation case]. Letter and circulars, 1954 (Folder 104: 4)
  - Friends Committee on National Legislation. Flyers, leaflets, circulars, newsletters, and testimony, 1955-1973 (Folder 104: 5)
  - Friends of Democracy. Clipping, 1950 (Folder 104: 6)
  - Friends of Edward J. Fitzgerald. Leaflet, ca. 1954 (Folder 104: 7)
  - Friends of Maria [re mental patient rights]. Circular letter, 1969 (Folder 104: 8)
  - Friends of Soviet Russia. Serial issues (Soviet Russia), 1922 (Folder 104: 9)
  - Friends of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade. Letters and circulars, 1938 (Folder 104: 10)
  - Friends of the First Amendment. Circulars, 1964-1965 (Folder 104: 11)
  - Friends of the Soviet Union. Pamphlet (The Decisive Year in the Soviet Union), 1931 (Folder 104: 12)
  - Froines, John. Clippings, 1974 (Folder 104: 13)
  - Fuchs, Klaus. Journal article, 1952 (Folder 104: 14)
  - Fund for Education in World Order. Circulars, 1969 (Folder 104: 15)
  - Fund for Peace. Circulars, and meeting materials re its Third National Convocation on the Challenge of Building Peace: The United States and China (New York City, 1971) (Folder 105: 1)
    1970-1971
  - Fund for the Advancement of Education [Ford Foundation project]. Annual report and Congressional hearing testimony, 1955-1957 (Folder 105: 2)
  - Fund for the Republic [Ford Foundation project] (Folder 105)
    - Fund for the Republic issuances (Folder 105)
      - General. Press releases, bulletins, report, leaflets, and pamphlets (The Fifth Amendment and the Immunity Act of 1954; The Threat to Academic Freedom), 1955-1957 (Folder 105: 3)
      - Three-year report, with cover letter by Robert M. Hutchins, 1956 (Folder 105: 4)
    - Material about the Fund for the Republic. Letters, clippings, journal articles, Congressional speeches, reports, bulletins, radio broadcast transcripts, and pamphlets (The American Legion Report on the Fund for the Republic; The Press and the Fund for the Republic; The Reece Report on Foundations), 1955-1962 (Folder 105: 5)
  - GI Civil Liberties Defense Committee. Circulars, flyers, petition, press releases, and newsletters (GI Defender), 1968-1971 (Folder 106: 1)
  - G.I. Defense Organization. Letters, refund check, circulars, flyers, press releases, and press coverage, 1969-1971 (Folder 106: 2)
  - GI dissidents (General) (Folder 106)
    - General. Leaflets, flyers, circulars, press releases, clippings, printed excerpts from books, and HISC study memoranda and staff study ("Subversive Activities Affecting the Military"), 1964-1973 (Folder 106: 3)
    - GI newspapers. Serial issues, 1968-1973 (Folder 106)
      - Aboveground; Ally; Arctic Arsenal; Bragg Briefs; Broken Arrow; Camp News; Fed Up!; Fun Travel Adventure; MDW Post; Military Intelligence (Folder 106: 4)
      - OM; Open Ranks; Open Sights; Pawn; Shakedown (Folder 106: 5)
      - Ultimate Weapon; Up Front; Your Military Left (Folder 106: 6)
  - GI Mobilization Committee/Open Sights. Flyer, 1969 (Folder 106: 7)
  - GI-Student Antiwar Action Committee [Emory University]. Circulars, 1969 (Folder 106: 8)
  - GI Voice. Serial issue, 1969 (Folder 106: 9)
  - GIs United against the War in Vietnam. Legal brief, flyer, clipping, and journal article, 1969 (Folder 106: 10)
  - Gainesville Committee to End the War in Vietnam [Gainesville, Florida]. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 106: 11)
  - Garment Center Committee to End the War in Vietnam [New York City]. Flyer, 1965 (Folder 106: 12)
  - Garrett Park Citizens for Peace [Washington, D.C.]. Printed letter to the editor, 1967 (Folder 106: 13)
  - Gays and lesbians (General). Flyers and serial issues (InterChange; Killer Dyke; Midwest Mattachine Newsletter), 1971-1972 (Folder 106: 14)
  - Gelders, Joseph S. Congressional hearing excerpts, letterhead data, and clippings, 1935-1946 (Folder 107: 1)
  - Genovese, Eugene. Clippings, court testimony excerpts, flyers, photocopy of index card file, and HUAC memoranda, 1947-1966 (Folder 107: 2)
  - George Washington University antiwar protests. Clippings, 1967 (Folder 107: 3)
  - Georgi Dimitrov Anniversary International Theoretical Conference (Sofia, Bulgaria, 1972). Speech transcripts and press coverage (Folder 107: 4)
  - Germany (East). East German English-language government issuances, including bulletins, pamphlets (The Background to American Literature since the War; Discover the GDR), and pictorial portfolio relating to Vietnam War, 1967-1973 (Folder 107: 5)
  - Gettysburg Vets' March to End the War in Vietnam. Circulars, 1966 (Folder 107: 6)
  - Ginsberg, Allen. Clippings, 1965-1967 (Folder 107: 7)
  - Goertzel, Ted. Clipping, 1965 (Folder 107: 8)
  - Goodlett, Carlton B. California gubernatorial election campaign literature, 1966 (Folder 107: 9)
  - Graham, Frank P. Letters, clippings, and letterhead data (American Friends of Spanish Democracy), 1936-1940 (Folder 107: 10)
  - Gravel, Mike. Letter by Gravel re Vietnam War, 1971 (Folder 107: 11)
    See also War No More
  - Gray, Jesse. Clipping, 1965 (Folder 107: 12)
  - Greater Boston Coordinating Committee to End the War in Vietnam. Newsletter, 1966 (Folder 107: 13)
  - Greece. Flyers and leaflets re solidarity with people of Greece, 1948-1969 (Folder 107: 14)
  - Greenbelt Committee for Peace [Greenbelt, Maryland]. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 107: 15)
  - Greene, Felix. Flyers and clippings, 1966-1968 (Folder 107: 16)
  - Greenwich Village Peace Center [New York City]. Circular letter, 1967 (Folder 107: 17)
  - Gregory, Dick. Clippings, 1966-1968 (Folder 107: 18)
  - Griswold, Deirdre. Clipping, 1965 (Folder 107: 19)
  - Group for Reconciliation of People Everywhere [GROPE; New Paltz, New Jersey]. Circulars and clippings, 1970-1971 (Folder 107: 20)
  - Guardian. Circular letters, serial issues, and pamphlet (Unite the Many, Defeat the Few), 1969-1975 (Folder 107: 21)
  - Gus Hall-Benjamin J. Davis Defense Committee. Circular letters and leaflet, 1965-1967 (Folder 107: 22)
  - Hamlin, Bryan. Printed appeals, 1966 (Folder 108: 1)
  - Hammett, Dashiell. Press release, leaflet, clippings, letterhead data, and HUAC memorandum, 1938-1940 (Folder 108: 2)
  - Harding, Timothy. HUAC memorandum, ca. 1965 (Folder 108: 3)
  - Harlem Community Council on Housing [New York City]. HUAC memoranda, ca. 1964 (Folder 108: 4)
  - Harlem Defense Council [New York City]. Flyers, clipping, pamphlet (Police Terror in Harlem), and HUAC memorandum, 1964-1966 (Folder 108: 5)
  - Harlem Solidarity Committee [New York City]. Press release, press coverage, and HUAC memoranda, 1964-1965 (Folder 108: 6)
  - Harris, David Victor. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 108: 7)
  - Harry F. Ward 90th Birthday Committee. Circular letter and commemorative program, 1963 (Folder 108: 8)
  - Hartke, Vance. Printed appeals, clippings, and journal articles, 1959-1971 (Folder 108: 9)
  - Harvard University antiwar protests. Circular letter and printed appeal, 1967 (Folder 108: 10)
  - Health Professionals for Peace in Vietnam. Clipping, 1967 (Folder 108: 11)
  - Healy, Daniel F. Clipping, 1965 (Folder 108: 12)
  - Help for Imprisoned War Objectors [Glenview, Illinois]. Flyer, 1969 (Folder 108: 13)
  - Hemispheric Conference to End the War in Vietnam (Montreal, 1968). Program and clippings (Folder 108: 14)
  - Henderson, Leon, and other staff members of the U.S. Office of Price Administration and Civilian Supply. Open letter from Martin Dies (chairman of HUAC) to Franklin D. Roosevelt, with supporting letters, letterhead data, clippings, journal articles, and excerpts from books, 1923-1941 (Folder 108: 15)
  - Herbert Aptheker Testimonial Dinner Committee. Circular letter and program, 1966 (Folder 108: 16)
  - Herz, Alice. Clippings, 1965 (Folder 108: 17)
  - High School Students against the War. Flyers and clippings, 1971 (Folder 108: 18)
  - Highlander Research and Information Center [Knoxville, Tennessee]. Letters, reports, leaflets, and circulars, 1966-1970 (Folder 108: 19)
  - Hiroshima Commemorative Committee [New York City]. Program, 1955 (Folder 108: 20)
  - Hispanics (General). Circulars, flyers, clippings, journal articles, and serial issues (Machete; La Raza), 1969-1974 (Folder 108: 21)
  - Hollis, Robert. Clippings, 1965-1966 (Folder 108: 22)
  - (Folder 108)
  - Hollywood Anti-Nazi League. Circular letters and Hollywood Now journal articles, 1937-1940 (Folder 109: 1)
  - Hollywood League for Democratic Action. Letter and flyer, 1940 (Folder 109: 2)
  - Hollywood Writers Mobilization. Letterhead data and serial issues (Hollywood Quarterly), 1945-1947 (Folder 109: 3)
  - Honolulu Record. Serial issues, 1948-1949 (Folder 109: 4)
  - Hughes for Senate Committee. H. Stuart Hughes Massachusetts election campaign literature, 1962 (Folder 109: 5)
  - Humanity Guild. Letters, organizational instructions, circulars, leaflet, and serial issue (Humanity), 1940-1962 (Folder 109: 6)
  - Hyde Park Committee to End the War in Vietnam [Hyde Park, Illinois]. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 109: 7)
  - Hyde Park Council of Organizations for Peace in Vietnam [Hyde Park, Illinois]. Clippings, 1966 (Folder 109: 8)
  - I. F. Stone's Weekly/I. F. Stone's Bi-Weekly. Serial issues, printed articles from the publication, and clipping re I. F. Stone, 1954-1971 (Folder 109: 9)
  - Icor (Association for Jewish Colonization in the Soviet Union). Letterhead data, souvenir program, and yearbook, 1931-1944 (Folder 109: 10)
  - Illinois Educators' Committee on Vietnam. Printed appeal, 1966 (Folder 109: 11)
  - Immigration (General) (Folder 109)
    - General. Letters, legal brief, leaflets, flyers, circulars, and pamphlets (The Loyal and the Disloyal; No Work Today!), 1942-1973 (Folder 109: 12)
    - Internal documents of miscellaneous and unidentified organizations opposed to McCarran-Walter Immigration Act. Letters, minutes, draft articles, and notes, 1937-1960 (Folder 109: 13)
    - Letters to Congressmen opposing McCarran-Walter Immigration Act, 1953-1956 (Folder 110: 1)
    - Congressional hearings. Printed reports (Communist Activities among Aliens and National Groups), 1949 (Folder 110: 2-3)
  - Imported Publications [book distributor; Chicago]. Catalog, 1975 (Folder 110: 4)
  - In Defense of the Right to Speak for Peace. Printed appeal, and list of endorsers, 1950 (Folder 110: 5)
  - In Fact. Serial issues (Folder 110)
    - 1941-1946 (Folder 110: 6)
    - 1947-1948 (Folder 110: 7)
  - Independent Citizens' Committee of the Arts, Sciences and Professions. Letters, election campaign contribution data, list of endorsers, printed appeal, program, and clipping, 1944-1946 (Folder 111: 1)
  - Independent Citizens Committee to Elect Herbert Aptheker Congressman [Brooklyn]. Leaflets, flyers, and circular letter, 1966 (Folder 111: 2)
  - Independent Committee on Vietnam of Columbia University. Circular, 1965 (Folder 111: 3)
  - Independent Labor League of America. Serial issues (Workers Age), 1939-1940 (Folder 111: 4)
  - Independent Party of Washington [State]. Election affidavit and circulars, 1950 (Folder 111: 5)
  - Independent Progressive Party. Letter, 1951 (Folder 111: 6)
  - Independent Socialist Clubs. Flyers and programmatic statements, 1957-1966 (Folder 111: 7)
  - Independent Voters' Committee of the Arts and Sciences for Roosevelt [re Franklin D. Roosevelt Presidential reelection campaign]. Circular letter and clippings, 1944 (Folder 111: 8)
  - Individuals (Miscellaneous) (Folder 111)
    - General. Dossiers, lists, letters, and HUAC memoranda, 1941-1967 (Folder 111: 9)
    - Photocopies of index card files, 1962-1975 (Folder 111: 10)
    - HUAC list of "Communists in the Government," undated (Folder 111: 11)
    - HUAC list of "Members of Front Organizations Residing in Washington, D.C. and Employed by the Federal Government," undated (Folder 111: 12)
  - Individuals against the Crime of Silence [re Vietnam War]. Printed appeals, petitions, list of endorsers, and clipping, 1967-1969 (Folder 112: 1)
  - Individuals for Non-Violent Revolution [San Jose, California]. Informant's report incorporating mailing list, 1965 (Folder 112: 2)
  - Indochina Information Service. Leaflets and flyers, 1971-1972 (Folder 112: 3)
  - Indochina Peace Campaign. Flyers, circulars, bulletins (Indochina Focal Point; Indochina Report; War Bulletin/Indochina Bulletin), and pamphlets (Vietnam: The Struggle for Peace; Women under Torture), 1972-1974 (Folder 112: 4)
  - Indochina Resource Center. Flyers, leaflets, circulars, bulletins (Indochina Chronicle), and pamphlet (Air War), 1971-1973 (Folder 112: 5)
  - Industrial Workers of the World. Flyers, leaflet, and pamphlet (The I.W.W. in Theory and Practice), 1920-1970 (Folder 112: 6)
  - Inman, Will. Clippings, 1967 (Folder 112: 7)
  - Institute for American Democracy [Washington, D.C.]. Circular letter, 1969 (Folder 112: 8)
  - Institute for Freedom in the Church [New York City]. Printed appeal, 1965 (Folder 112: 9)
  - Institute for Policy Studies [Washington, D.C.]. Correspondence, internal documents, flyers, Congressional speech, and clippings, 1968-1971 (Folder 112: 10)
  - Institute of Pacific Relations [New York City]. U.S. Senate Internal Security Subcommittee summary of testimony, and pamphlet (Land of the Soviets), 1942-1957 (Folder 112: 11)
  - Integrated Education. Circular letter, 1965 (Folder 112: 12)
  - International Committee of Conscience on Vietnam. Printed appeal, 1966 (Folder 113: 1)
  - International Committee of Solidarity with the Youth and People of South Vietnam. Circular letter, 1964 (Folder 113: 2)
  - International Committee on African Affairs. Letter by Max Yergan, 1939 (Folder 113: 3)
  - International Committee to Defend Eldridge Cleaver. Printed appeal, 1969 (Folder 113: 4)
  - International Committee to Free South Vietnamese Political Prisoners from Detention, Torture and Death. Letter, flyers, and list of endorsers, 1973 (Folder 113: 5)
  - International Confederation for Disarmament and Peace. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 113: 6)
  - International Conference on Alternative Perspectives on Vietnam (Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1965). Program and statement (Folder 113: 7)
  - International Days of Protest Peace March Committee [San Francisco]. Flyer, 1966 (Folder 113: 8)
  - International Fur and Leather Workers Union. Flyers, union election literature, American Federation of Labor statements, digest of judicial cases involving union leaders, and list of Communist Party members in union, 1940-1961 (Folder 113: 9)
  - International Labor Defense (Folder 113)
    - General. Letters from International Labor Defense to Unemployed Council, leaflets, circulars, and printed articles and printed excerpts from Communist Party press, 1925-1944 (Folder 113: 10)
    - Labor Defender. Serial issues and printed articles from the journal, 1926-1937 (Folder 113: 11)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union. Circular letters, bulletins, serial issues (Dispatcher), and texts of legal motions in case of United States vs. Fujimoto et al, 1940-1967 (Folder 113: 12)
  - International Longshoremen's Association. Circular and serial issues (Shape-Up), 1937 (Folder 113: 13)
  - International Socialists. Flyers, serial issues (I.S.; Workers' Power), and pamphlets (The American Working Class; Women Workers), 1969-1971 (Folder 114: 1)
  - International Student Movement for the United Nations. Press releases, 1971 (Folder 114: 2)
  - International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers. Flyer, Congress of Industrial Organizations press releases, and National Labor Relations Board press release and report of hearings, 1950-1954 (Folder 114: 3)
  - International Union of Revolutionary Writers. Serial issues (International Literature), 1935 (Folder 114: 4)
  - International Union of Students. Serial issues (World Student News), printed article, and flyer, 1971-1973 (Folder 114: 5)
  - International Workers Order (Folder 114)
    - General. Circular, clippings, convention proceedings, pamphlet (A Youth Fraternal Order), and New York state police report, 1931-1954 (Folder 114: 6)
    - Fraternal Outlook. Serial issues (Folder 114)
      - 1939-1940 (Folder 114: 7)
      - 1942 (Folder 114: 8)
      - 1949 (Folder 114: 9)
  - Inter-University Committee for Debate on Foreign Policy. Circulars, printed appeals, and Congressional report (The Anti-Vietnam Agitation and the Teach-In Movement), 1965-1967 (Folder 115: 1)
  - Intourist [Soviet travel agency]. Letter and bulletin, 1935-1939 (Folder 115: 2)
  - Iranian Students Association. Flyers and pamphlet (On the Shah's Celebration), 1971-1972 (Folder 115: 3)
  - Ireland. Flyers, clipping, and serial issue (United Irishman) re solidarity with people of Ireland, 1969-1974 (Folder 115: 4)
  - Jacobs, Paul. Clipping, 1965 (Folder 115: 5)
  - Japan Congress against A and H Bombs. Bulletin, 1965 (Folder 115: 6)
  - Japan Peace in Vietnam Committee. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 115: 7)
  - Japanese American Citizens League. Conference proceedings (Special Emergency National Conference, Salt Lake City), 1942 (Folder 115: 8)
  - Japanese American Committee for Democracy. Letter to HUAC, 1944 (Folder 115: 9)
  - Jeannette Rankin Brigade [re Vietnam War]. Leaflets, resolution, and clippings, 1967-1968 (Folder 115: 10)
  - Jefferson Bookshop [New York City]. Order form, 1966 (Folder 115: 11)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science [New York City]. Circulars, press releases, statement, program, and clippings, 1944-1954 (Folder 115: 12)
  - Jeremiah Stamler, M.D. Legal Aid Fund. Letter, circular letters, and statement, 1966-1967 (Folder 115: 13)
  - Jewish Campaign for the People's Peace Treaty to End the War in Indochina. Leaflet, 1971 (Folder 115: 14)
  - Jewish Cultural Clubs. Open letter, 1971 (Folder 115: 15)
  - Jewish Currents. Circular letters and printed excerpts, 1957-1972 (Folder 115: 16)
  - Jim Hayes Defense Fund. Circulars, 1970 (Folder 115: 17)
  - Johnny Appleseed Patriotic Publications. Leaflets and serial issues (New Patriot), 1969-1970 (Folder 115: 18)
  - Joint Anti-Fascist Refugee Committee. Printed appeals, flyers, and financial statement, 1945-1951 (Folder 115: 19)
  - Joint Fall Peace Fund. Printed appeal, 1971 (Folder 115: 20)
  - Kansas State College Vietnam teach-in. Leaflet, flyers, and clippings, 1967 (Folder 115: 21)
  - Kastenmeier, Robert W. Schedule, press release, and clipping re informal hearing on Vietnam called by Congressman Kastenmeier in Madison, Wisconsin, 1965 (Folder 115: 22)
  - Kennedy, John F., assassination conspiracy theories. Newsletter and printed articles, 1968-1971 (Folder 115: 23)
  - Kepner, Diane. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 115: 24)
  - Kiger, Peter. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 115: 25)
  - King, Gaylord. Clippings, 1966 (Folder 116: 1)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr. Circular letters, leaflets, flyers, Congressional speeches, Church League of America pamphlet, and clippings, 1967-1971. (Folder 116: 2)
    See also Southern Christian Leadership Conference
  - Klein, Mark. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 116: 3)
  - Knudson, Kenneth. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 116: 4)
  - Koch, Chris. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 116: 5)
  - Koch, Harold M. Clippings, 1966-1967 (Folder 116: 6)
  - Korea (North). North Korean government English-language issuances (Folder 116)
    - General. Press releases, circular letters, radio broadcast transcripts, and serial issues (Korea Today; People's Korea; Pyongyang Times), 1970-1973 (Folder 116: 7)
    - Pamphlets (Answers to the Questions Raised by the Iraqi Journalists' Delegation; Appeal?to the South Korean Fellow Countrymen; The Common Struggle of the Revolutionary Peoples of Asia against U.S. Imperialism Will Surely Win Victory; A Reply to the President of the Korean Affairs Institute in Washington; South Korean Reality; U.S. Imperialism: The Sworn Enemy of the Korean People), 1969-1973 (Folder 116: 8)
  - Ku Klux Klan. Membership application, oath of allegiance, and HUAC statements, 1965 (Folder 116: 9)
  - Kurki, Irving. Circular letter and clipping, 1965-1966 (Folder 116: 10)
  - Labor (General) (Folder 116)
    - General. Flyers, leaflets, circulars, and excerpts from printed sources, 1923-1974 (Folder 116: 11)
    - Serial issues (Ammunition; Distributive Worker; New Voices; People's Daily World; Power and Light; Spokesman; Sunday Worker; T.W.O.C. Bulletin; Voice of the Federation; We the People), 1937-1971 (Folder 116: 12)
    - Material about labor, including anti-labor publications. Clippings, journal articles, press release, pamphlet (Labor Monopolies, or Freedom), and internal HISC notes, 1931-1975 (Folder 116: 13)
  - Labor Committee for Peace in Vietnam. Printed announcement and pamphlet (The Unspeakable War), 1966 (Folder 117: 1)
  - Labor League for Peace [Los Angeles]. Minutes, 1952 (Folder 117: 2)
  - Labor Sports Union of America. Serial issues (Sport and Play), 1931 (Folder 117: 3)
  - Labor Today. Letter, circulars, and serial issues, 1962-1975 (Folder 117: 4)
  - Labor Youth League. Circular letter, printed announcement, and pamphlet (We Accuse McCarthyism), 1954 (Folder 117: 5)
  - Labor's Non-Partisan League. Program and clipping, 1938-1941 (Folder 117: 6)
  - Lamont, Corliss. Clippings, 1966-1967 (Folder 117: 7)
  - Landau, Saul. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 117: 8)
  - Laos. Pamphlet (Laos and the Victorious Struggle of the Lao People against U.S. Neo-Colonialism) published by Neo Lao Haksat Publications (no place of publication indicated), 1969 (Folder 117: 9)
  - Law Students against the War. Clipping, 1967 (Folder 117: 10)
  - Law Students Civil Rights Research Council. Circular letters and leaflets, 1965-1972 (Folder 117: 11)
  - Lawson, John Howard, and Dalton Trumbo. Amici curiae briefs in related case hearings of Lawson vs. United States and Trumbo vs. United States before U.S. Supreme Court, 1949 (Folder 117: 12)
  - Lawyers against Test Oaths for the Bar [California]. Circular letter, 1951 (Folder 117: 13)
  - Lawyers Committee on American Policy towards Vietnam. Letters, circulars, bulletins, printed appeals, clippings, Congressional speech, and HUAC notes, 1965-1970 (Folder 117: 14)
  - Lawyers Committee to End the War [New York State]. Circulars, 1971 (Folder 117: 15)
  - League for Industrial Democracy. Circular letters, leaflets, resolution, and bulletins, 1965-1969 (Folder 117: 16)
  - League for Mutual Aid. Letter and leaflet, 1935 (Folder 117: 17)
  - League for the Protection of Minority Rights [Pittsburgh]. Serial issue (Appeal to Reason), 1939 (Folder 117: 18)
  - League of American Writers. Pamphlets ("We Hold These Truths?"; Writers Take Sides), 1938-1939 (Folder 117: 19)
  - League of Women Voters. Journal articles, 1954-1957 (Folder 117: 20)
  - Lee, Oliver. Transcript of radio interview, 1966 (Folder 117: 21)
  - Left Review [British publication]. Serial issue, 1935 (Folder 117: 22)